{
    "quiz":[
        {
            "question":"Critically acclaimed Citizen Kane was directed by which American director?",
            "answer":"Orson Welles",
            "wrong1": "Martin Scorsese",
            "wrong2": "Steven Spielberg",
            "wrong3": "Alfred Hitchcock",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393a49149411e13e61ab70"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following is the most popular film George Lucas was involed in?",
            "answer":"Star Wars",
            "wrong1": "American Graffiti",
            "wrong2": "THX 1138",
            "wrong3": "Howard the Duck",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393b40149411e13e61ab73"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following was NOT nominated for best animated film in the 2004 oscars?",
            "answer":"The Incredibles",
            "wrong1": "Finding Nemo",
            "wrong2": "Brother Bear",
            "wrong3": "The Triples of Belleville",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393b61149411e13e61ab74"
        },
        {
            "question":"Who played the star role: Harry Potter?",
            "answer":"Daniel Radcliffe",
            "type": "input",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393bc1149411e13e61ab75"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which actor played a wizard, a vampire, and a crimefighting billionaire?",
            "answer":"Robert Pattinson",
            "wrong1": "Christopher Lee",
            "wrong2": "Ben Affleck",
            "wrong3": "Kevin Conroy",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393a49149411e13e61ab70"
        },
        {
            "question":"In Sam Raimi's Army of Darkness what name does Ash give to his double-barreled shotgun?",
            "answer":"Boomstick",
            "wrong1": "Broomstick",
            "wrong2": "Bangarang",
            "wrong3": "Sasha",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393b40149411e13e61ab73"
        },
        {
            "question":"In the first Back to the Future film, what year does Marty McFly find himself trapped in?",
            "answer":"1955",
            "type": "input",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393b61149411e13e61ab74"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following films did NOT have John Williams as the lead composer?",
            "answer":"Rogue One: A Star Wars Story",
            "wrong1": "War of the Worlds",
            "wrong2": "The Adventures of Tintin",
            "wrong3": "Saving Private Ryan",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393bc1149411e13e61ab75"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following have NOT voiced Mickey Mouse?",
            "answer":"Roy Disney",
            "wrong1": "Wayne Allwine",
            "wrong2": "Bret Iwan",
            "wrong3": "Chris Diamantopoulos",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393a49149411e13e61ab70"
        },
        {
            "question":"Before the adaptation was handed to Peter Jackson, who was originally hired to direct the live-action adaptation of The Hobbit?",
            "answer":"Guillermo del Toro",
            "wrong1": "Ralph Bakshi",
            "wrong2": "Christopher Nolan",
            "wrong3": "Tim Burton",
            "type": "multi",
            "tag": {
                "_id": "624335d9eac7f554ed8ec213",
                "tag": "Entertainment: Film"
            },
            "user": "62393b40149411e13e61ab73"
        }
    ]
}